Tell me.
I love you.
I love you, Reo.
Dude, why'd your alarm go off?
Cause I bet my life on 3 PM snack time.
Kenji!
Hiroko.
Sorry, we weren't trying to interrupt.
This is a real shocker.
How much did you hear?
Turns out your destined partner was Mai.
"They haven't found out it's Aiko."
So? Are you gonna go out with her?
What? Isn't that obvious?
We're officially dating now.
What?
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 3]
Here's your lunch.
Hey, no way, something's off!
So, she's dealing with "that".
Yup, "that".
Oh yeah, "that". "That".
- Guy problems.
- For sure.
Huh? A guy?
Isn't that obvious?
We're officially dating now.
What?
What do people do
when they're… dating?
Huh? Reo's girlfriend?
- Wanna see a picture? Her name is Mai.
- We do! What sort of person is she?
She's cuter in person.
Mai is a college student.
- She's a maid? How feminine!
- Yup.
So, what will you do?
What will I do?
- Morning.
- Reo, is it true?
This "Mai" is your girlfriend?
Oh, she's—
- Reo! Let's have a match.
- What?
I won't lose today!  "Keep quiet about it."
All right.
Good work!
- Kasumi lost to Reo, again.
- Dude, what the hell!
Reo, why do keep stealing my ball?
- Your fault for being full of openings.
- Openings?
- Where?
- Everywhere.
Everywhere?!
(T/N: The word for "openings" and "like" sound the same)
- Here we go again.
- You're having fun though.
I'm not having fun at all, thanks to him.
[Maid Cafe | Spica]
Is our rivalry gonna continue forever?
Sure, it's fun.
You know,
I think we should tell them about us.
Then what about "Mai"?
I can say we broke up.
That way, people won't find out you’re actually "Mai".
There's no problem staying as we are.
No problem?
Isn't it a pain?
Storing your clothes, and changing in a restroom every time—
It's fine.
Wouldn't you prefer walking around with "Mai"? She's girlfriend material.
Don't misunderstand my feelings.
What?
Isn't "Mai" more up to your standard?
I didn't fall for you as "Mai".
The one I like, is "Aiko".
If you really don't get it,
I'll make you understand.
Who is he?
Oh yeah, Ritsuki said we're getting some new part timers.
This means I can quit, right?
Which means I'll get you all to myself.
Anyways, I'll go quit.
Give me a minute.
Quit? Yeah, go for it!
That was quick.
Can't blame me, look at our newest worker.
It seems like the chest area is a bit tight.
I'm the newcomer, Ikumi Morikawa.
[No man has escaped her grasp. A truly carnivorous girl]
[Ikumi Morikawa]
Are you Mai?
Yes, I am.
I heard you were a college student but...
you don't look it.
- Chief, where should this go?
- Just put it wherever.
That's her younger brother, Takumi.
We're twins!
Since we're fraternal, we don't look alike.
[Ikumi's younger twin brother. A level-headed hottie!]
[Takumi Morikawa]
We meet again.
Isn't Ikumi such a cutie?
You're relieved of your position.
Do you two know your shifts next week?
- Yes, sir.
- Let's discuss this in the back.
What's with this angry feeling?
[Anger, anger, anger, anger]
My recommendation is the Jiggle-Wiggle Pudding!
Does she think it's so easy being a maid?
Welcome back, Master!
That Master smiles only for me.
- I'm back!
- What?
She's late.
- Order is up.
- Thanks.
Thank you for waiting. Here is your Drawing Omurice!
Do you have any requests?
- I'd like Ikumi to draw.
- What?
Here I am, Master!
I've been waiting!
There you go!
Master, let's continue with our board game—
Master, let's play
cards together!
- I'm, uh...
- Now, now, over at this table!
Do you have a ten?
Mai.
[Pissed, pissed, pissed]
Damn her...
One Twinkle Dream Parfait.
Whoa, you have talent!
Master, welcome—
What's the meaning of this?
Welcome back!
To think we would meet again… this must be fate!
- Again? What do you mean, "again"?
- First I've seen her.
I feel like we were together in a past life.
No, I'm absolutely sure!
Don't just decide that yourself.
Don't decide that for yourself, please?
I appreciate the customer service, but I'm her boyfriend.
And that's that.
So what?
This must be love at first sight!
What?
Thank you for waiting. Here is your coffee.
What's with that chick? Pushing the cleaning to me.
You're a student, right?
- I am.
- Do you come here often?
- Sort of...
- I see!
Here you go.
Thanks.
You're quite bold, kissing behind the store.
That's none of your business.
Does he bother you?
He's my younger twin brother.
I changed my mind, I'm not quitting.
What?
I can't let this end in a loss.
Quitting was your idea.
I'll make sure we meet, and match my days off to yours. It's fine, right?
If you continue working as "Mai", what about us?
Will we date while lying, forever?
Well...
I want to properly say I'm dating "Aiko".
Isn't it weird for enemies to be dating?
- I want to openly date you as "Aiko".
- And that's what I can't stand.
It's too embarrassing. How could I tell everyone?
So that's how you thought of this.
Do as you want.
I'm leaving.
Reo!
I understand how you feel, but I think you went overboard.
I had no intention of hurting him.
Words can hurt someone, more than you think they do.
You're right.
I should properly apologize to him.
Did you hear? We have a transfer student.
A transfer student?
[Year 2 Class A]
[Ikumi Morikawa]
Morikawa will sit...
Reo!
This must really be fate!
l will become your girlfriend.
- Seriously?
- What's with this development?
Plus, Reo has a girlfriend.
Is the other Morikawa here?
Of course! After all, he's my younger brother.
[Takumi Morikawa]
Today, we have a new classmate.
His name is Takumi Morikawa.
Seriously?
Due to my father's job, we came from Turkmenistan.
Turkmenistan is in Central Asia.
Central Asia?
Pleased to meet you.
[Strawberry Milk]
I want to openly date you as "Aiko".
And that's what I can't stand.It's too embarrassing. How could I tell everyone?
Words can hurt someone, more than you think they do.
- Reo—
- Reo!
Let's eat lunch together.
Can I? So you like yakisoba bread?
- What's with her?
- She disgusts me.
I like sweeter bread, so let's eat that instead.
Why? Come on!
What about melon bread?
Go on, hurry up.
Go on.
Why are you suddenly confessing to Reo?
Reo is for everyone.
- So what?
- We're saying, don't get close to him.
- How pitiful.
- What?
Can't complain without a posse? Pathetic.
- The hell?
- You think you're cute or something?
Of course I do. Way cuter than you.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh my god, I'm so sorry!
- For real?
- Yikes!
Stop it already.
Aiko, you have the wrong bathroom.
Stop being fucking lame! Go on, leave.
Just go.
She has the worst timing.
Hey, are you okay?
Stop being meddlesome.
I'm use to it.
Don't be ridiculous.
Even if you're "used to it", you'll still be hurt.
Here.
Who are you?
I'm… a passerby—
A tomboy is acting all high-and-mighty.
I hate girls.
I hate you too.
What's her deal?
Ikumi.
Did something happen again?
I'm fine.
More importantly, I've become motivated.
Mr. Koike!
Break time!
Good work out there.
Morikawa?
The basketball team's manager?
Yes, it was something Mr. Koike decided on the fly.
I thought you said a manager would distract the players.
I told him the same thing.
Then I'll also be the girls team manager—
I have to go pick up my son.
I leave the rest to you, Ms. Oyama.
Mr. Koike!
Hold on a second!
Good work.
I'm the new team manager, Takumi Morikawa.
You're the manager of the girl's team?
As I recall, you're my classmate... Kasumi?
That's right, I am.
Something the matter?
Ikumi,
I have something to ask about our training regime.
- Okay.
- This way.
You two are glued at the hip.
Same part time, and now extracurriculars.
Ikumi gets misunderstood by girls, so I have to protect her.
"Misunderstood", huh...
Wait,
did I mention a part time job?
Oh, I heard from... Hiroko.
Have we met?
Don't think so. We just met in the classroom earlier.
I make an effort never to forget girls I've met before.
Don't touch her so easily. Aiko is my exclusive toy.
- Your toy?
- Yeah.
Aiko, you've forgotten "that".
- "That"?
- You know, "that".
- "That".
- What's "that"?
"That" can only mean "that"!
- "That" is...
the fact that I wanted to speak to you, face-to-face.
Me too.
I'm sorry.
I said something in poor taste the other day.
I don't really understand "dating".
I might...
hurt you again.
Ai!
- Where did she go?
- What should we do about these refreshments?
You're finally in my grasp.
I have no intention of letting go.
If you don't want to go out with me, scream.
- That's not it.
- Where could she have gone?
The bathroom?
It's not that I dislike going out with you.
I'm...
scared of everyone finding out that I'm "Mai".
I'm not confident
I'm a girl that matches your level.
I…
do not know what to do.
But…
I don't want you to hate me.
Like I'd ever hate you.
I'm also sorry.
You weren't mentally prepared.
We'll go at your pace.
Having you
loving me like this,
is more than enough.
Aiko... Aiko, let's keep this all a secret,
until you're ready to tell everyone
that you're "Mai".
Okay.
Things are getting interesting.
[Next time]
Keeping a secret is a real trial.
I think I'll tell Morikawa everything.
I wonder if Mai backed down for me.
Mai is... similar to someone, isn't she?
I have to remain the normal "Aiko Kasumi", so no one finds out.